(Bernadette:)Should we tell
everyone not to come?
(Howard:)No. I want to do this.
(Bernadette:)Okay. Well, I'll keep
it together if you can.
Okay. (chuckles)
(voice breaking):
I'm not making any promises!
(Stuart:)Glad you guys
could make it.
(Raj:)Of course.
(Penny:)Wow, it looks really
pretty in here.
(Stuart:)Yeah, turns out half a dozen
menorahs really sets a mood.
(Leonard:)So, Stuart,
have you thought about
(Leonard:)what you'd do
if Howard sells the house?
(Stuart:)And there goes the mood.
(Sheldon:)Hi. Hello.
(Sheldon:)Oh, and a special
hello to Leonard,
(Sheldon:)who needs to be
mentioned by name.
(Leonard:)Subtle.
(Sheldon:)But you got it, right?
(Howard:)Hey, guys.
(Amy:)Hey.
Hi.
Hello.
(Howard:)I just want
everyone to know,
(Howard:)uh, tonight's not
a sad occasion.